<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Personal Examples &#8211; All My Respect</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/personal/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>dedicated to the man who deserves all my respect</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Mon, 22 Apr 2019 03:27:30 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Dedication</title>
		<link>/dedication/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 14:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal Examples]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=107</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I respect your dedication to friends and family. When the relationship has struggles you don&#8217;t just throw it away. I admire your dedication to work. Doing things right and putting in the extra effort even when people may not notice. I appreciate your dedication to living out your beliefs. I value your dedication to us, <a href="/dedication/">Continue reading &#8594;</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I respect your <strong>dedication</strong> to friends and family. When the relationship has struggles you don&#8217;t just throw it away.</p>
<p>I admire your <strong>dedication</strong> to work. Doing things right and putting in the extra effort even when people may not notice. </p>
<p>I appreciate your <strong>dedication</strong> to living out your beliefs.</p>
<p>I value your <strong>dedication</strong> to us, and making our relationship enjoyable and not just reliable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Computers&#8230; Cars too!</title>
		<link>/beyond-computers-cars-too/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal Examples]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=91</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Not only can he fix my computer, he can fix my car too! ]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My man is definitely a computer geek. No question on his prowess in the networking field. He can talk about computer like car enthusiasts talk about cars.<span id="more-91"></span></p>
<blockquote><p>Examples: &#8220;This mother board is compatible with these parts&#8221;; &#8220;in that year this company camp out with these things&#8221;; &#8220;this part is the same as that part, it&#8217;s just called something else&#8221;; &#8220;you can make these better parts work by doing this&#8221;; &#8220;the company manufactured x amount of these parts&#8221;; &#8220;this part can be used for that part&#8221;; &#8220;even though the documentation is wrong, you can still use these, and this is how&#8221;; &#8220;I&#8217;m sure I have a part that will work for that&#8221; &#8230; you get the idea, amazing!</p></blockquote>
<p>Having established his geekiness, you might assume his knowledge or skills end there. You&#8217;d be wrong. He is not your typical geek. Not only can he fix my computer, he can fix my car too!</p>
<p>As an example:</p>
<p>Our car needed a new radiator. They no longer make the radiator. There is a new radiator, but it doesn&#8217;t even work as well as the original which was barely good enough. Bad choice. He found someone who builds a better radiator that will work. Knowing what type of radiator would be best point #1. Finding best radiator point #2. Being able to change a radiator point #3. Being able to make a radiator that isn&#8217;t specifically designed for that vehicle work with all the little parts that need to be tweaked, and in some cases designed, extra bonus points. Making it work the first time, bonus, bonus points. Not afraid to get help or do the work MEGA bonus point. He&#8217;s just so good.</p>
<p>Conclusion: I have an AMAZING man AND a new radiator. YAY!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sharing my Hobbies</title>
		<link>/sharing-my-hobbies/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 12:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal Examples]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=64</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[My man proved his love, by not only let me go to the craft store, but also participated in choosing yarn for my projects.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I enjoy crochet&#8230; ok, I&#8217;m addicted. <span id="more-64"></span>I especially like it because it gives me something to do while riding in the car or watching TV. I like getting yarn on ebay because it a good price and they have a much better selection then Wal-Mart, especially since they&#8217;re almost never stocked well. We also have a very small yarn shop. But those are my options in town. And with ebay it&#8217;s really hard if I&#8217;m trying to get specific colors or textures and I don&#8217;t know which brand/color I need.</p>
<p>On this basis, we recently went to Vegas for a concert, so of course I wanted to go somewhere to look for the yarn I needed for two particular projects. Shopping is definitely not my man&#8217;s idea of a good time, and a craft store is near top of the list of worst places to go shopping. However, he knows we don&#8217;t have much here and he wants me to be happy, so he agreed to the craft store. This in and of it self is a wonderful thing but it doesn&#8217;t stop there. I didn&#8217;t have my sisters there to help me decide on yarn, and it is not often that you find exactly what you want right away, so I needed, or really wanted anyway, some help deciding what to get. Now we&#8217;re getting into the nightmare realm. Not only does he not want to have anything to do with choosing yarn, he also does not want to feel inadequate to choose yarn. Textures and colors are not his fortay.</p>
<p>My man proved his love, by not only let me go to the craft store, but also participated in choosing yarn for my projects. He also proved again how much more than adequate he is, he is extremely good at figuring things out, even when it comes to my things like yarn. He was so helpful in helping me choose the best options for my projects from what was available, no one else could have helped me more. Selfishly I would love his help with my stuff all the time, he is just so good at seemingly everything I need. But I try not to push him into unpleasant things too often, and I am extremely grateful to him for being there when I &#8220;need&#8221; him, even for things that may seem silly, like yarn or dead lizards.</p>
<p>Besides helping me when I need him, he also shares in my hobbies by actively listening to things that I&#8217;m doing, or getting, or want to try. He also encourages me in the things I do. He is a true friend and self-sacrificing man. A wonderful example of what a real man truly is.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>dedication to work</title>
		<link>/dedication-to-work/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 11:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal Examples]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=30</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I can be proud of anything you do at work because I know you've done it they way is should be.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I really respect your dedication to your job.</p>
<p>Giving extra effort.</p>
<p>Doing your best to have things done &#8220;correctly&#8221;.</p>
<p>I can be proud of anything you do at work because I know you&#8217;ve done it they way is should be.</p>
<p>with my admiration,<br />
LLW</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
