<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Inspiration &#8211; All My Respect</title>
	<atom:link href="/allmyrespect/category/inspiration/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/allmyrespect/</link>
	<description>dedicated to the man who deserves all my respect</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Mon, 22 Apr 2019 03:27:30 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>I thought we would just eat by candlelight!</title>
		<link>/allmyrespect/i-thought-we-would-just-eat-by-candlelight/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Inspiration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=79</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Here’s a good example of a wife showing her husband respect, admiration, and love he needed from her: Pastor E.V. Hill served for many years as pastor of Mt. Zion Missionary Baptist Church in Los Angeles. When E.V. first began in the ministry, he was a hard worker who wanted to provide for his wife, <a href="/allmyrespect/i-thought-we-would-just-eat-by-candlelight/">Continue reading &#8594;</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here’s a good example of a wife showing     her husband respect, admiration, and     love he needed from her:</p>
<p>Pastor E.V. Hill served for many years as pastor of Mt. Zion Missionary Baptist Church in Los Angeles. When E.V. first began in the ministry, he was a hard worker who wanted to provide for his wife, but he was also a young preacher who struggled to make enough money just to pay for the necessities.</p>
<p>Pastor Hill’s wife appreciated his efforts to protect and provide for her, even though some months there wasn’t enough money to pay all the bills. One night, he came home and noticed immediately that the house was dark. When he opened the door, he saw that his wife, Jane, had prepared a candlelight dinner. He loved the idea, but when he went to the bathroom to wash up, he flipped the light switch and nothing happened. Then he went to the bedroom and tried the lights. Again… there was nothing. The entire house was dark.</p>
<p>He went back and asked his wife why the lights didn’t work. Jane began to cry and said, “You work so hard, but it’s rough. I didn’t have enough money to pay the electric bill. I didn’t want you to know about it, so I thought we would just eat by candlelight!”</p>
<p>Dr. Hill described this experience with deep emotion: “My wife could have said, “I never had this happen in the home I was raised in.” But she didn’t berate or blame him. Instead she said, “Somehow we’ll get these lights back on, but tonight let’s eat by candlelight.”</p>
<p>Our calling to love and respect is a calling regardless of what the other person does. It’s sacrificial. It’s in the scriptures. It works!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>I believe in you</title>
		<link>/allmyrespect/i-believe-in-you/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 06:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Inspiration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=59</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[in the things that are important to you and in the way you choose to live your life&#8230; I believe that you can accomplish anything you set out to do, that you have many talents and the wisdom to use them well&#8230; I believe that you have what it takes to overcome obstacles and to <a href="/allmyrespect/i-believe-in-you/">Continue reading &#8594;</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>in the things that are important to you and in the way you choose to live your life&#8230;</p>
<p>I believe that you can accomplish anything you set out to do, that you have many talents and the wisdom to use them well&#8230;</p>
<p>I believe that you have what it takes to overcome obstacles and to grow from every experience life brings your way&#8230;</p>
<p>I believe in your courage, your compassion, your integrity, and your strength.</p>
<p>I believe in your goodness&#8230;</p>
<p>I believe in you.</p>
<p><em>by Bobbie Burrow</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>I appreciate all the little things you do</title>
		<link>/allmyrespect/i-appreciate-all-the-little-things-you-do/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 08:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Inspiration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=57</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I wonder if you know how much I appreciate all the little things you do&#8230; Thank you for the way you reach out to hold my hand at unexpected moments, the way you cuddle me at night, the way you can make me laugh with just a look, the way you pick me up when <a href="/allmyrespect/i-appreciate-all-the-little-things-you-do/">Continue reading &#8594;</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I wonder if you know how much I appreciate all the little things you do&#8230;</p>
<p>Thank you for the way you reach out to hold my hand at unexpected moments, the way you cuddle me at night, the way you can make me laugh with just a look, the way you pick me up when I&#8217;m feeling down, and the way you share things I enjoy, even if they&#8217;re not your favorites&#8230;</p>
<p>Today I just want to let you know how much I appreciate the little things&#8230;</p>
<p>and to thank you for loving me in all the special ways you do.</p>
<p><em>by Terry Matz</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
