<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Practical Help &#8211; All My Respect</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/help/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>dedicated to the man who deserves all my respect</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Mon, 22 Apr 2019 03:27:30 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>10 Practical Ways to Honor Your Hubby</title>
		<link>/10-practical-ways-to-honor-your-hubby/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 10:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=101</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[by: Grace Driscoll on Feb 08, 2012 (http://pastormark.tv/2012/02/08/10-practical-ways-to-honor-your-hubby) 1. Pray faithfully. When I pray for my husband, the Holy Spirit softens my heart and his, and I learn to trust God with my marriage. 2. Grow personally. Time with Jesus and the Bible, studying and repenting are essential to honoring our husbands. 3. Encourage regularly. <a href="/10-practical-ways-to-honor-your-hubby/">Continue reading &#8594;</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>by: Grace Driscoll <small>on Feb 08, 2012 (<a href="http://pastormark.tv/2012/02/08/10-practical-ways-to-honor-your-hubby">http://pastormark.tv/2012/02/08/10-practical-ways-to-honor-your-hubby</a>)</small></div>
<article>
<h2>1. Pray faithfully.</h2>
<p>When I pray for my husband, the Holy Spirit softens my heart and his, and I learn to trust God with my marriage.</p>
<h2>2. Grow personally.</h2>
<p>Time with Jesus and the Bible, studying and repenting are essential to honoring our husbands.</p>
<h2>3. Encourage regularly.</h2>
<p>As you encourage him, you will begin to understand all the ways you can be thankful rather than grumbling.</p>
<h2>4. Inquire daily.</h2>
<p>Don&#8217;t just ask what he did during the day. Rather, ask how he is doing so you can find ways to serve him if he is stressed or celebrate with him if he is excited.</p>
<h2>5. Pursue intimately.</h2>
<p>When you work on the friendship, the intimacy becomes more mutually enjoyable, so be willing to step up and pursue him.</p>
<h2>6. Play frequently.</h2>
<p>When a marriage is all work and no play, it feels like a business partnership instead of a loving partnership, so plan fun.</p>
<h2>7. Listen attentively.</h2>
<p>Women love to talk, but it is important to learn to listen in order to get to know your husband better.</p>
<h2>8. Speak respectfully.</h2>
<p>Make sure your tone isn&#8217;t out of bitterness or unrighteous anger. His ability to lead will suffer if you are disrespectful.</p>
<h2>9. Correct privately.</h2>
<p>When you see sin or error, do not try to belittle him publicly, but instead prayerfully approach him with your concerns in private.</p>
<h2>10. Laugh loudly.</h2>
<p>Back to having fun, don&#8217;t allow life to get so serious that you don&#8217;t ever laugh together.</p>
</article>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Does It Mean to Respect Your Husband?</title>
		<link>/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband/</link>
				<comments>/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 11:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=97</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[by: Grace Driscoll on Feb 07, 2012 (http://pastormark.tv/2012/02/07/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband) &#160; &#8220;. . . let the wife see that she respects her husband.&#8221; Ephesians 5:33 &#160; Do you want a joyful and unified marriage that glorifies God? In order to obtain oneness and worship our Lord with our marriages, as women and wives we need to correctly <a href="/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband/">Continue reading &#8594;</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>by: Grace Driscoll <small>on Feb 07, 2012 (<a href="http://pastormark.tv/2012/02/07/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">http://pastormark.tv/2012/02/07/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband</a>)<br />
</small></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<article>
<blockquote>
<h3><em>&#8220;. . . let the wife see that she respects her husband.&#8221; Ephesians 5:33</em></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p></blockquote>
<p>Do you want a joyful and unified marriage that glorifies God? In order to obtain oneness and worship our Lord with our marriages, as women and wives we need to correctly understand the need for respect. Respect <a href="http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=ephesians%205:33&amp;version=AMP">is</a> to notice, regard, honor, prefer, defer to, encourage, love, and admire. Men and women were created with equal worth but different roles. Though men are not exempt from respecting their wives, God created the woman to help (<a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/gen+2%3A18/">Genesis 2:18</a>) and respect her husband (<a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/eph+5.33/">Ephesians 5:33</a>).</p>
<p>The Bible provides principles for how to respectfully help our husbands, but it does not give us many methods. Women are prone to ask other women what methods they use as respectful helpers, or to read books such as <a href="http://www.amazon.com/RealMarriageTheTruthAboutSexFriendshipandLifeTogetherHardcover/dp/140020383X/?tag=pandt-20"><em>Real Marriage</em></a> seeking to be told what to do. What follows are some of the lessons I’ve learned from the mistakes I’ve made over the years. My prayer is that it encourages you to be the respectful wife that God has created you to be.</p>
<h1><strong>Heads of Respect</strong></h1>
<p>Respect starts in our heads, and includes our mind and thoughts. Disrespect also starts in our heads and can over time affect our hearts and hands. <a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/james+1.14-15/">James 1:14–15</a> describes this perfectly: “But each one is tempted when he is drawn away by his own desires and enticed. Then, when desire has conceived, it gives birth to sin; and sin, when it is full-grown, brings forth death.”</p>
<p>Disrespect starts when we think things like: <em>That was a dumb decision he made</em>,<em> I can do better than that. I wish he were more like _____</em>, or, <em>I’ll just fix all the things he does wrong. I hope the kids don’t grow up to be like him. When he is out of town life is easier. I won’t ask him because he won’t understand.</em> If you are thinking this way toward your husband and let it continue, it will seep into your heart and eventually come out in your words and actions toward your husband.</p>
<p>For some of you this is new. For others you understand that you need to respect your husband, but are having a difficult time doing so. Regardless of where you find yourself today, the following is what I recommend for you to start.</p>
<p>Confess your sin of disrespecting authority to God and your husband, and be willing to listen to the Holy Spirit’s conviction for change.</p>
<p>Begin developing new habits of biblical thinking by being thankful for your husband’s gifts and strengths, rather than being bitter about his weaknesses and shortcomings. I encourage you to take time to observe your husband closely and even start a journal or make a list of things you appreciate about him.</p>
<h1><strong>Hearts of Respect</strong></h1>
<p>If our hearts are working toward respect, our mouths will follow, because “out of the abundance of the heart the mouth speaks” (<a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/matt+12.34/">Matthew 12:34</a>). If our hearts abound with disrespect, our mouths will spew disrespectful words. As women, our words are often motivated or withheld, because of our emotions. Do you tend to respond to your husband with criticism or with silence?</p>
<p>When you talk about him in public or with others do you tear him down or build him up? Are you careful not to gossip about him, or do you freely share your issues with others? This includes prayer requests, women’s Bible studies, and female accountability relationships that degenerate into gossip, busy bodying, and disrespecting our husbands in the name of ministry. Are you a wife who criticizes, contradicts, or sneers at your husband? Do you do this in front of other people? Do you “joke” about his lack of abilities or his way of doing things? Do you cut him down in front of the kids?</p>
<p>Our battle with words goes all the way back to the Garden of Eden when Eve used her words to ask her husband to sin with her. Her intention was not to bless him, but to excuse her sin and have him join her in it. We continue to fight the same war with our mouths today, but God gives us the Holy Spirit for wisdom and strength to continue being redeemed.</p>
<p>Also, it’s important to remember that we don’t change our husbands—the Holy Spirit does! Use your words to pray for and help him instead of belittling him. Use your words to pray for yourself that you would practice self-control (<a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/eph+4.29/">Ephesians 4:29</a>).</p>
<p>Sometimes we don’t even hear ourselves, because our words can be subtle disrespect, so we might need others whom we trust to help us assess our hearts and mouths. Ask your husband or a godly woman, or both, if your words are respectful, and be willing to listen without blame shifting or excusing your sin. We cannot grow in respect if we disregard those who point out our disrespect.</p>
<h1><strong>Hands of Respect</strong></h1>
<p>God created women to be helpers, which is a reflection of his character. God said, “It is not good that man should be alone,” so he created a helper for Adam (Genesis 2:18). It’s important to note that the word “helper”<em> </em>does not denigrate the wife; in fact, God is also referred to as our helper (<a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/psalm+10.14/">Psalm 10:14</a>; <a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/psalm+118.6-7/">118:6-7</a>; <a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/heb+13.6/">Hebrews 13:6</a>).</p>
<p>As a helper, a wife is called to become a companion in her husband’s God-given calling. This is what <a href="http://www.esvbible.org/search/1+cor+11.7-9/">1 Corinthians 11:7–9</a> means. Upon marriage, a woman’s life changes as she joins her husband in his life’s course. That looks different for me than it does for your marriage because each of our husbands is unique.</p>
<p>For starters, prayerfully consider the following ways to have respectful hands:</p>
<h2><em>Hands That Pray </em></h2>
<p>Prayer softens our hearts and our husband’s hearts. If you only pray for him to change, then you won’t see your own sin too. Prayer reminds us of our total dependence upon God.</p>
<p>When I pray for Mark, he feels respected and loved. I look at his calendar for the day and pray for teaching sessions, meetings, appointments, safety, wisdom, and other things God brings to mind. We also enjoy prayers of thankfulness together when we see God’s grace in our lives. When Mark is sad, upset, stressed, or discouraged, I offer to pray out loud with him.</p>
<h2><em>Hands That Touch</em></h2>
<p>Physical affection is key to intimacy. If your husband enjoys touch, you probably can’t go overboard on this one. If your husband is more reserved, you can still express comfort through holding hands, neck rubs, and meaningful kisses.</p>
<p>Sex for the purpose of oneness usually doesn’t just “happen” at the end of a long day without working toward it throughout the day. Don’t get into a habit of only touching him when he is leaving the house once a day. Rather, learn to enjoy playfulness that leads to deeper intimacy and sex. Try meeting him for lunch appointments when possible. Instead of demands when he arrives home from work, greet him at the door with a hug or kiss. Text him during the day to let him know you are thinking about him.</p>
<h2><em>Hands That Feed </em></h2>
<p>Take time to plan a menu for the week (or month) so you aren’t throwing unhealthy things together for dinner or tempted to always eat out. There are many recipe and cooking websites that offer healthy meal ideas. Your husband will have more mental, physical, and emotional energy if he is not eating simple carbs and sugar all day. I’m not saying he can’t cook if he likes to, but be attentive to nutrition. Sitting down to regularly enjoy good meals together is also a welcoming way to nurture your friendship with your husband.</p>
<h2><em>Hands That Hunt and Fish</em></h2>
<p>Be unselfish. Mark loves baseball, so I have attended many games and learned how baseball works. I often watched him play in high school. Our three boys also love baseball, so I spend countless hours at the field for all their games. In return, Mark knows I don’t like to shop alone, so he takes me to my favorite stores every so often and helps pick out what looks nice. He also loves to study the culture by watching some of the popular TV shows, so I watch shows with him that wouldn’t be my first choice. The point is to do activities that your husband likes to do and have fun with it, not be disgruntled.</p>
<h2><em>Hands That Open the Bible</em></h2>
<p>Grow your relationship with Jesus. If you aren’t getting fed through Bible reading, prayer, and personal repentance, then it will be impossible to know how to serve and respect your husband.</p>
<p>Since respect is a command, God doesn’t leave us clueless and unable: he will give us the wisdom and strength to carry it out. We <em>have </em>to stay connected to Jesus in order to keep our husbands a priority over tasks, kids, other people, and the pull of culture. I tried respecting Mark without keeping Jesus first, and it was a disaster no matter how hard I tried. I used to think I didn’t have time for daily Bible and book reading, but we just need to use the time that God already gives us. Anytime the order of godly (1) woman, (2) wife, (3) mother, and (4) friends gets switched, we commit idolatry and end up in misery. As a mother of five, I learned to pray for God to show me moments throughout the day to use for reading, and the Holy Spirit is faithful to remind me of those times if I am willing to listen.</p>
</article>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/what-does-it-mean-to-respect-your-husband/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Show Your Husband True Respect</title>
		<link>/how-to-show-your-husband-true-respect/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=87</guid>
				<description><![CDATA["Wives, respect your husbands." Paul seemed to think that was necessary to include in his letter to the Ephesians. As Miss Piggy would say, "Who, moi?" Yes, moi. I'm tired of seeing husbands mistreated by their wives...I did it to mine for years. I learned the hard way, and he paid the price, so let me redeem that hardship by sharing with you how I now show him respect.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><cite><span>By</span> <a href="http://www.ehow.com/members/shannonny.html">Shannon Nee</a>, 					eHow Member <img src="http://i.ehow.com/images/22X22AUT_badge.gif" alt="Rating" /> </cite></p>
<div><a href="http://i.ehow.com/images/GlobalPhoto/Articles/4544312/LoveHusband-main_Full.jpg"><img class="alignleft" src="http://i.ehow.com/images/GlobalPhoto/Articles/4544312/LoveHusband-main_Thumb.jpg" alt="Wives, respect your husbands." width="175" height="116" /></a></div>
<p>&#8220;Wives, respect your husbands.&#8221; Paul seemed to think that was necessary to include in his letter to the Ephesians. As Miss Piggy would say, &#8220;Who, moi?&#8221; Yes, moi. I&#8217;m tired of seeing husbands mistreated by their wives&#8230;I did it to mine for years. I learned the hard way, and he paid the price, so let me redeem that hardship by sharing with you how I now show him respect.<span id="more-87"></span></p>
<ol id="intelliTxt">
<li>
<div>Step <span>1</span></div>
<p>COMPLIMENT HIS WORK<br />
Men are very connected with their work, and a lot of self-worth is invested in what they do to make money or otherwise &#8220;show&#8221; themselves to the world. I take every opportunity, always sincerely, to compliment my husband on any achievement or success, even if it&#8217;s small, that has to do with his place in the world&#8211;especially among other men. I just try to let him know he&#8217;s my main contender, no matter what!</li>
<li>
<div>Step <span>2</span></div>
<p>APPRECIATE HIS HUMOR<br />
When he&#8217;s being funny (and he often is), I smile and laugh as much as I honestly can. I don&#8217;t patronize him, but I do try to encourage him! During the years he sheltered his heart I could hardly get him to repeat some silly old <a style="border-bottom: 0.075em solid darkgreen ! important; font-weight: normal ! important; font-size: 100% ! important; text-decoration: underline ! important; padding-bottom: 1px ! important; color: darkgreen ! important; background-color: transparent ! important; background-image: none; padding-top: 0pt; padding-right: 0pt; padding-left: 0pt;" href="http://www.ehow.com/how_4544312_show-husband-true-respect.html#" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">joke</a>. When he&#8217;s humorous with me now, that means he&#8217;s opening his heart and showing love. And reciprocating the good feeling means I&#8217;m respecting him.</li>
<li>
<div>Step <span>3</span></div>
<p>SHARE HIS THOUGHTS<br />
Part of learning to be a respectful wife was learning to really hear what my husband said. I try to listen carefully, thoughtfully, when we talk together. I want to make my replies intelligent and supportive. It is a strong sign of respect to show him that I value his thoughts and concerns enough to weigh them with love and wisdom before I speak.</li>
<li>
<div>Step <span>4</span></div>
<p>LET HIM BE HIM<br />
Day in and day out I shelled my husband with a constant barrage of critical talk. That&#8217;s right: nagging. He couldn&#8217;t <a style="border-bottom: 0.075em solid darkgreen ! important; font-weight: normal ! important; font-size: 100% ! important; text-decoration: underline ! important; padding-bottom: 1px ! important; color: darkgreen ! important; background-color: transparent ! important; background-image: none; padding-top: 0pt; padding-right: 0pt; padding-left: 0pt;" href="http://www.ehow.com/how_4544312_show-husband-true-respect.html#" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">cook</a> right, talk right, or even watch TV right. I don&#8217;t know what I thought I was trying to accomplish&#8230;but it sure backfired! Now, to show him respect, I try to keep my mouth shut if I don&#8217;t like something. And if I don&#8217;t like something, I have to ask myself why, and also, how important is it? Nine times out of 10 it&#8217;s some quirk I have a thing about that doesn&#8217;t matter a bean.</li>
<li>
<div>Step <span>5</span></div>
<p>USE GOOD TIMING<br />
I used to think that whatever I had to say to my husband had to be said immediately, or as close to immediately as possible. I had a lot of growing up to do! When I learned the value of good timing, communication between us improved dramatically. Men, like women, need space and down time. When he&#8217;s enjoying a game, time on the computer, or just sitting and thinking, I leave him alone. If I need to talk to him, I keep an eye on his activities, and wait for an appropriate &#8220;in.&#8221; If the topic is unpleasant, I save it for a daytime discussion when he&#8217;s rested and positive. If I want something, I wait until his team wins!</li>
<li>
<div>Step <span>6</span></div>
<p>BE NICE IN PUBLIC<br />
Haven&#8217;t you seen her? Have you been her? The woman who thinks it&#8217;s &#8220;funny&#8221; to insult and undercut her husband in public? This is a surefire way to get him to really hate you. I tried to not do this, too much, but sometimes temptation got the better of me when I wanted to boost my self-esteem at his expense. How much better now when I show him respect instead, by laughing at his <a style="border-bottom: 0.075em solid darkgreen ! important; font-weight: normal ! important; font-size: 100% ! important; text-decoration: underline ! important; padding-bottom: 1px ! important; color: darkgreen ! important; background-color: transparent ! important; background-image: none; padding-top: 0pt; padding-right: 0pt; padding-left: 0pt;" href="http://www.ehow.com/how_4544312_show-husband-true-respect.html#" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">jokes</a>, praising him about some accomplishment, and letting him tell a story or have a conversation without interrupting him.</li>
<li>
<div>Step <span>7</span></div>
<p>DISTANCE THE KIDS<br />
I used to start arguments with my husband in front of the kids. Oh, what a shame that was. Talk about disrespectful: How about trying to make the most important man in their lives look like a fool? I beg you, women, please don&#8217;t do what I did. If you feel some serious fracas coming on, keep it down until you can be alone with your husband and have it out, as evenly and quietly as possible. There is untold damage in tearing down a father. Build him up, praise him, respect him instead. It is an incredible blessing for <a href="http://www.ehow.com/children/">children</a> to have a father that their mother respects.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>8 Ways to Show Your Husband You Love Him</title>
		<link>/8-ways-to-show-your-husband-you-love-him/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=85</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Men and women experience love in very different ways. Most people are not conscious of this as they go through their lives, and so they attempt to show their love to people of the other sex in the same way they want it shown to them, in the same way they think of it naturally, without considering how the other person views it.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Men and women experience love in very different ways.  Most people are not conscious of this as they go through their lives, and so they attempt to show their love to people of the other sex in the same way they want it shown to them, in the same way they think of it naturally, without considering how the other person views it.<span id="more-85"></span></p>
<p>There are certain things that are necessary to feel loved that are shared among nearly all people, regardless of gender.  This includes things like time together, touching, communicating, and other things of this nature.  This type of thing is worth of its own article, so for this article, I&#8217;m sticking with things that are either specific with regards to wives with their husbands, or at least more emphasized. Women, if you&#8217;re reading this, realize that just like you, a man doesn&#8217;t feel loved just because you say &#8220;I love you&#8221;.  That doesn&#8217;t mean you shouldn&#8217;t say it (you should), but you can&#8217;t just leave it at that&#8230; and most men won&#8217;t tell you that they don&#8217;t feel loved.  Many of them don&#8217;t even realize that is what is bothering them, they just know they aren&#8217;t happy, and possibly that it has to do with their relationship, but not be able to put it into a solid concept that they don&#8217;t feel loved. I&#8217;m a man<br />
.  I know that most of the things I need to feel loved, when they are boiled down to basics, are the same for most other men.  There may be a few here and there that one of the things below do not apply to, or a few here and there where there is another essential addition.  If you are one of those men, and reading this, please add them in the comments.  For the vast majority, however, I think this list covers the basics.</p>
<p>So, with no further ado, ladies, here are some basic ways you can show your husband you love him</p>
<p>1.Respect Him</p>
<p>The most effective way to make a man feel unloved is to disrespect him, especially in front of others.  If you have any desire at all to take good care of your husband, and make him feel loved, do not ridicule him, overrule him, or dismiss him in front of someone else.  It&#8217;s bad enough to do it in private (you really do NOT need to use these methods&#8230; find another way to convey your message), but in public you might as well slap his face.</p>
<p>2.Admire Him</p>
<p>This is related to the first, but from the other side.  Respecting him is more about avoiding disrespect than an overt display of respect.  Admiring him, on the other hand is explicitly about conveying to him, by words or gestures, what it is that you like about him.  This can be body language, like giving him &#8220;elevator eyes&#8221; when he&#8217;s watching, if you like his body, or it can be words, like telling him that you love his sense of humor.  You should always make sure that you use something appropriate to the circumstances, however&#8230; telling him you love his sense of humor while you&#8217;re at his father&#8217;s funeral together might not be a good idea.  You also need to vary this, finding new (or infrequently used) little things to tell him you like on a fairly regular basis.  If you have trouble coming up with stuff on your own (are you sure you&#8217;re with the right guy for you?), then just instantly tell him when he takes an action you like&#8230; if he comes around and opens you car door for you, and you like it, tell him so.  Always hearing the same thing, like &#8220;I love your sense of humor&#8221;, makes it lose its power for this.  It gets to the point where he won&#8217;t really believe you, thinking you&#8217;re just saying it to manipulate him.</p>
<p>3.Let Him &#8220;Overhear&#8221; You Praise Him</p>
<p>This works wonders, but has to be used infrequently, and with caution.  It doesn&#8217;t work, and can feel manipulative, if you pretend like you don&#8217;t know he&#8217;s there, but he can tell that you do.  It&#8217;s much better, and safer, to ACTUALLY praise him to others, and occasionally he&#8217;ll be nearby when you do so, and overhear it.  This technique actually works if you do it outright, too, as long as you don&#8217;t over do it.  That is, you can flat out say to someone &#8220;My husband is great, he does for me&#8221;, with him sitting beside you, and it will make him feel like you respect and admire him (see above).</p>
<p>4.Drop Everything</p>
<p>This is a little thing that has major effects.  One of the most effective ways of showing someone you love them is to make them top priority, to the point where you stop everything you&#8217;re doing, whatever it is, to focus on them.  That is, you step away from the computer, let the baby play by herself, turn off the TV, stop cooking dinner, whatever it is you&#8217;re doing, and go to that person and specifically show them that they are your central focus RIGHT THEN.  This is particularly effective when you first see them after a separation (ie when you or they get home from work, etc.).</p>
<p>5.Notice His Strengths</p>
<p>This is similar to admiring him, but specific to his strengths.  That is, if it&#8217;s hard for you to get the lid off the jar, and you know he can, go ask him, telling him something like &#8220;I&#8217;m not strong enough to open this.  Can you do it for me?&#8221;.  If his strength is math, ask him to calculate the price per ounce of something (or a similar feat of arithmetic), telling him it&#8217;s too hard for you.  Don&#8217;t lie in this&#8230; he&#8217;ll know.  Just make a point of asking him to help anywhere that you know is a strength of his that complements a weakness of yours.  As noted, this can be physical or mental&#8230; &#8220;Can you move this for me, I can&#8217;t do it?&#8221; or &#8220;Can you help me figure out how to word this?&#8221;.  Just like admiring him, though, overuse of this in one area tends to lower its effectiveness, eventually becoming more annoying than complementary.</p>
<p>6.Forgive His Weaknesses</p>
<p>Your husband has his weaknesses.  All men do, and all women, too, for that matter.  Do NOT use his weaknesses against him.  If you use them to try to manipulate him, if you bring them up any time it&#8217;s not absolutely necessary, he will start feeling like you don&#8217;t respect him in that area.  This applies to showing off areas where you are noticeably stronger than him, too, unless it&#8217;s somewhere he feels he doesn&#8217;t need to (or can&#8217;t) compete, which is generally areas that are not considered masculine, or areas where it is widely acknowledged that special talent is required, like singing.</p>
<p>7.No Comparisons</p>
<p>One of the worst things a wife can do is compare her husband to an ex, whether husband or boyfriend.  Doing so is bad even if you are saying that your husband is better in some way.  Men understand that they were not necessarily the first person you were with, the first person you loved, but that doesn&#8217;t mean they want it brought into their conscious awareness.  And if you compare your husband poorly, as in he&#8217;s not as good at this or that, then this is multiplied.  You are disrespecting him, pointing out his weaknesses, AND reminding him that you were with other men before him.  That&#8217;s just asking to bring up negative emotions and associate them with you.</p>
<p>8.No Guilt Trips</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a classic, portrayed in uncountable movies and television shows&#8230; the wife gives her husband a guilt trip until he does what she wants.  Manipulating someone is a bad idea.  Clumsily manipulating them is even worse, but manipulating them at all is bad.  This has two sides, in that it&#8217;s bad for both the person being manipulated and the one doing it.  The person being manipulated, by definition, feels like he is having his power of choice taken from him.  If you feel that it&#8217;s still completely your choice, then you are not being manipulated.  That doesn&#8217;t mean that someone isn&#8217;t TRYING to do so, but if you still feel like it&#8217;s entirely your choice, then they are not succeeding.  Now, for someone who DOES feel like their choice is being taken from them, they will resent this strongly.  One of the most powerful motivating factors in a human life is the desire to be free, to prove that you can make your own decisions, and that those decisions matter.  Messing with this desire is playing with fire&#8230; if the person you are manipulating notices it, even later on, after the fact, they will resent it.  Since, in this case, we are talking about your spouse, that means that resentment is likely to be there, even if it eventually fades, as a factor when he thinks about you for the rest of your lives together.  It may be small, maybe even so small that he&#8217;s not consciously aware of it, but it will, none the less, be there.Manipulating someone is bad for the person doing the manipulation, also.  When you attempt to manipulate someone, you attempt to take some of their humanity from them.  They will, as mentioned above, resent this, generally resenting even an unsuccessful attempt.  But it&#8217;s just as bad for the person doing it, especially if they are doing it to their spouse, because it takes away from your concept of the person you&#8217;re trying to manipulate as a person, an individual, and instead turns them into more of an object.  Objects can be generally counted on to have the same output when given the same input.  Thinking of people in this way robs them of their humanity, their power of individual choice, making you respect, and love, them less.  Presumably, if you&#8217;re reading this article, that&#8217;s not exactly what you have in mind.</p>
<p>So there you have it, 8 ways to show your husband that you love him.  Some are things to actively do, some are things to actively make sure you DON&#8217;T do, but when they are all put together, and included with the things that all people need to feel loved, your husband will know, and feel, that you love him.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treat him like a V.I.P.</title>
		<link>/treat-him-like-a-v-i-p/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=70</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Respect him verbally, intellectually, and physically. ]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center">Respect him verbally, intellectually, and physically.<span id="more-70"></span></p>
<p><strong>Verbally </strong><br />
<em>Cut out (ok…cut back) complaining and add in compliments. </em></p>
<p>If you want to have a peaceful, happy marriage, learn the art of the compliment. Compliments are like magnets and the more you compliment your husband the more he will be attracted to you. Begin to notice when he does it right and verbally encourage him by complimenting him at least once a day. If you are having a hard time thinking of anything to admire, consider these categories: physical traits, mental skills, financial strengths, spiritual growth, or healthy relationships with others (children, parents, or friends).</p>
<p>You may be asking “Hey, why should I compliment him when he NEVER compliments me?” Because, if you want your marriage to grow and bloom, you’ll have to water it with kindness and encouragement. Then, as he sees your sincere efforts, he will begin to change too. Don’t give up.</p>
<p>If you do need to bring up a difficult issue, place it between two compliments, also known as a “Compliment Sandwich.” Here’s an example, “Honey, I know how hard you work for our money and that Sally’s braces will be expensive, but I need your decision before her appointment tomorrow. I hope we can do this for her, but if you want to wait, I trust your judgment. What should I tell the orthodontist? ”</p>
<p><strong>Intellectually</strong><br />
Men like to solve problems and fix things. So appeal to his intelligence by asking him to help you solve a problem. Instead of saying “Clean up your camping stuff, this garage is a mess!” Try, “I’d like your help with something. Could you figure out a storage system for all the camping supplies?”</p>
<p>Don’t imply that he isn’t smart. Instead of saying “I think you are wrong about….” Say, “I’m confused about…please explain it again.” (Remember to keep your tone of voice free of sarcasm.)</p>
<p>Ask for his help on Spiritual matters too. Ask him to explain a passage of Scripture or ask him to pray for you when you are going through a difficult time. If your husband is not the spiritual leader in your home, continue to pray for him and ask him if there is anything you are doing that is hindering his relationship with God.</p>
<p>Men don’t give a lot of weight to feelings—show them facts and they’ll be more likely to listen. For example: if he wants to buy a car that you think is too expensive, don’t launch into a hissy-fit, write out your monthly expenses and ask him what other things should be cut out in order to buy his car. Let the facts speak for you.</p>
<p>When you cannot reach an agreement, instead of trying to wear him down by nagging or crying ask him, “Is that your final decision or can I still try to convince you? If it’s his final decision, then honor it. It’s freeing—let him carry the responsibility of your family.</p>
<p><strong>Physically </strong><br />
Physically-ask what he would like you to do and then, do it. Find out what his top three needs are. Ron likes the laundry done, sex twice a week (guaranteed!) and he likes me to keep my “girly-make-up stuff” off of the bathroom counter. If these top needs are met, he’s content and easy to get along with. I know it sounds simple, but each of us have different things that make us feel loved and appreciated. You won’t know what he wants unless you ask him.</p>
<p>Be aware of your body language. You can communicate disrespect by rolling your eyes, crossing your arms, or slamming doors. Reflect your new decision to respect your husband in your heart, mind, and body.</p>
<p><strong>Change your attitude and actions</strong><br />
Respect is both a verb and a noun: an action and an attitude so begin today to respect your husband in thought, word, and deed. He will be more willing and able to give you the love and affection you need if he is respected and admired. When I began to respect my husband, he was skeptical at first. However as he saw that I was committed to change, he began to treat me differently—lovingly. We now teach at couples’ events, helping others discover the blessings of true love in action.</p>
<p>Ask the Lord to strengthen you as you obey His word.</p>
<p><em>Philippians 4:13 I can do all things through Christ who strengthens me.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to show Respect</title>
		<link>/how-to-show-respect/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=68</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[In most societies, this is an obvious one. There's an etiquette for showing respect. Everyone knows it. And most people observe it. But, in the US, most people lack these formalities. So, let me give you some general ideas for showing respect for your husband.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In most societies, this is an obvious one. There&#8217;s an etiquette for showing respect. Everyone knows it. And most people observe it. But, in the US, most people lack these formalities. So, let me give you some general ideas for showing respect for your husband.<span id="more-68"></span></p>
<ol>
<li>Pay attention to body language. There&#8217;s a way of looking at a person that implies contempt or defiance. The look is hard to describe, but we all know it in others. Now, look for it in yourself. Do you roll your eyes when your husband&#8217;s talking? Do the corners of your mouth turn up? And so on. This is in the Bible, <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Proverbs 30:17</span>,<em><br />
&#8220;The eye that mocks at his father and despises to obey his mother, the ravens of the valley will pick it out and the young eagles shall eat it&#8221;.</em></li>
<li>Listen to how you say it&#8211;as well as what you say.  There is a way of saying, <em>&#8220;Yes, Honey&#8221;</em> that means &#8220;<em>No way, Buster!&#8221; </em> We call it sarcasm.  Good words that connote bad things.</li>
<li>Give your husband the benefit of the doubt. Assume he knows best. In other words, say &#8220;yes&#8221; unless there&#8217;s a strong reason to ask &#8220;why&#8221;.</li>
<li>When you have to question him or even disregard what he says, do it without defying him. There&#8217;s more than one way to say No. Choose the humblest way.</li>
<li>Never ever overrule him in front of the children!</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="http://www.gracebaptist.ws/sermons/notes/FamilyLife/FamilyLife13.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Excerpt from Grace Baptist Church</a></p>
<blockquote><p>•  Express faith in his       decision and ability.</p>
<p>• Leave him notes (men respond better to the written word) that tell him how much you value who he is as a person (and sometimes for his work).</p>
<p>•  If he botches a task       at home, don’t sigh, roll your eyes,       and mutter at him; instead, thank him       for trying.</p>
<p>•  Make positive suggestions         without demanding an immediate answer.         Ask him to reflect on it for a while.</p>
<p>•  Listen to his upsets       and don’t take his anger personally.</p>
<p>•  Let him vent when he       needs to.</p>
<p>•  Encourage him in areas         where he doesn’t feel secure and       let him know you stand behind him.</p>
<p>•  When he makes a decision         you’re not in favor of, listen.</p>
<p>•  Talk about his positive         strengths in front of the children.</p>
<p>•  Praise him at least once         a day.</p>
<p>•  Discover the uniqueness         of his personality and learn to understand         him and communicate better with him.</p>
<p>•  Accept his maleness and         celebrate the differences that come       from this.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Tips on Proper Geek male Maintenance</title>
		<link>/5-tips-on-proper-geek-male-maintenance/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=66</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Geek Males often work in fields that cause them to have to think a great deal and work long or irregular hours. This generally results in what I call “hurty brain”**Hurty Brain stems from the repeated misfiring of synapses that occurs when a question is asked of a geek that is light years behind what they specialize in. ]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ol>
<li>Geek Males often work in fields that cause them to have to think a great deal and work long or irregular hours. This generally results in what I call “hurty brain”*<span style="font-weight: bold;">*Hurty Brain stems from the repeated misfiring of synapses that occurs when a question is asked of a geek that is light years behind what they specialize in. </span><span id="more-66"></span>Talking to them when they are fresh off dealing with the “raging stupid” is likely a bad idea as they aren&#8217;t always able to distinguish you from the enemy while suffering from &#8220;Hurty Brain&#8221;.
<p>Crack them a beer or pour them a glass of whatever they prefer and let them be for a while. Giving them time to read webcomics or kill a few things on the PS3 lets them unwind, allows the brain to repair itself and gives the beast within time to settle down.</li>
<li>Geek Males need play time. Whether it’s Xbox, Warcraft, or building PC’s from parts, geek guys need time to engage in said activities. Without harassment. You may not know a Tauren from a Master Chief, but just because you may not get it doesn’t mean he doesn’t think its pretty dang awesome.Side note: This is true for any hobby, really. If you haven’t found a way to give your guy a couple of nights to do what he likes without interruption, you’re going to find yourself single fairly soon.If you engage in the same activities (and enjoy them – no fair just “pretending” so you can be included), that opens up the possibilities. Heck, girls like Magic just as much as boys do and any Geek worth his salt loves a woman who knows how rock the DPS. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11.2.0/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />
<p>2a. NOTE: <span style="font-style: italic;">Geeks do have a tendency to lose track of time and may go over limit</span>. Pulling your geek away from his hobbies may at times seem daunting, but I&#8217;m sure you can think of a way to get his attention ;-).</li>
<li>Let’s talk about movies. Be fair. Really. Asking a guy to watch a “chick flick” is already asking a lot. (On a side note, I’ve never really understood why women ask that. I mean, why would you <span style="font-style: italic;">want </span>to torment a guy? ::grin:: Don’t you have girlfriends to go to the movies with?)Solution? Trade off. If you’re going to ask him to watch Steel Magnolias, you’d better be ready to watch Buckaroo Banzai. Know what I mean?</li>
<li>Buying him a present? Want to know what he wants?  Giftcards. Giftcards. Giftcards.Why? Because Geek males are horridly self sufficient. You’re going to buy him a book or a game and you’ll be –so- proud of yourself that you remembered he wanted the new David Weber hardback when you were at the mall.But by the time you’re ready to give it to him he’ll walk into the house with a bag from Best Buy or Borders because he got it for himself. Yeah, I’m looking at <span style="font-style: italic;">you</span>.</li>
<li>Lastly, and perhaps the most challenging&#8230;engaging the geek male in conversation. Obviously you got through the door if you&#8217;re reading this list and taking notes, but knowing how to communicate with the opposite sex is what makes or breaks any relationship.Learn how to speak Geek or at least learn to actively listen to the Geek in your life.For reference, let&#8217;s define what &#8220;geek&#8221; means, and for that we call upon the words of a college professor: Being a geek means possessing and being passionate about knowledge that no one cares about or considers.
<p><span style="font-style: italic;">No one. </span></p>
<p>So, you can see that the geek male is largely ignored throughout his natural life, even amongst his own people. There is hope because being male, geek males understand the logic of an argument even if the rest of the natural world believes the argument to be nonsense. The key is to counter his geek with your own.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s got to be something inside you, or easily accessible that you can call into discussion as a parallel to form an argument. Draw the parallel and you&#8217;re good. He may not understand it in perfect context, but he will acknowledge your passion for it and your attempt at relating.</p>
<p>He may also secretly wet himself a little.</li>
</ol>
<p>brought to you by GeekGirlDiva, <a href="http://geekgirldiva.entertainmentearth.com/2009/06/5-tips-on-proper-geek-male-maintenance.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">view the whole article here</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Steps Towards Respecting Your Husband (Even When You Don’t Feel Like It)</title>
		<link>/10-steps-towards-respecting-your-husband-even-when-you-dont-feel-like-it/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 01:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=49</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[A wise woman once told me, “If you want a truly fine husband, respect him at the level at which you want him to reach. A man will usually not rise above the level at which his wife  respects him.” This is a general principle, not a hard and fast rule because God does not put accountability or responsibility for a man’s character on his wife. Nevertheless, strong evidence indicates a woman holds great power to make or break a man. In his book His Needs, Her Needs, Willard Harley amends the saying “Behind every great man is a great woman” to “Behind every great man is an admiring wife.”]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em> by 			    Cyndie Hamley</em></p>
<p>With downcast eyes, Kathryn confided, “I have a hard time respecting my husband. I want to be obedient to God’s command, but I don’t want to be dishonest to my feelings.”</p>
<p>God doesn’t command a wife to <em>feel</em> respectful toward her husband. She is to <em>be</em> respectful. Her responsibility is to obey God; not her feelings.<span id="more-49"></span></p>
<p>A wise woman once told me, “If you want a truly fine husband, respect him at the level at which you want him to reach. A man will usually not rise above the level at which his wife  respects him.” This is a general principle, not a hard and fast rule because God does not put accountability or responsibility for a man’s character on his wife. Nevertheless, strong evidence indicates a woman holds great power to make or break a man. In his book <em>His Needs, Her Needs,</em> Willard Harley amends the saying “Behind every great man is a great woman” to “Behind every great man is an admiring wife.”</p>
<p>Something in a man needs the respect of his wife. He thrives and grows toward godliness when his need is fulfilled. This explains why God emphatically says, “The wife must see to it that she respects her husband” (Ephesians 5:33 NASB).</p>
<p><strong>10 Steps Towards Respecting Your Husband</strong></p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Pray for him daily</strong> and trust God to answer your requests.</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Pray for his well-being, wisdom, protection, blessings, guidance, knowledge, spiritual maturity, success, purity, strength in temptation, etc.</li>
<li>Look for God’s answers to your prayers.</li>
<li>Thank God for working in your family.</li>
<li>Thank God for your husband.</li>
<li>Pray for your attitude.</li>
</ul>
<ol type="1">
<li><strong>Remember</strong> that God has put your husband in a position of leadership, and <em>He will lead you through your husband.</em></li>
<li><strong>Make a list</strong> of your husband’s qualities that you appreciate. Review and add to your list regularly.</li>
<li><strong>Tell your husband</strong> what you appreciate about him. Tell others what you appreciate about him.</li>
<li><strong>Don’t criticize</strong> your husband to others – especially your children.</li>
<li><strong>Look for the positive</strong> side of things that you may find irritating. If you find it boring when he spends time telling you about his bad day, remember that at least he is talking to you, spending time with you, sharing his concerns with you, bringing you into his confidence, and giving you the chance to be an encourager and helper.</li>
<li><strong>Respond</strong> to his loving advances with enthusiasm.</li>
<li><strong>If you are concerned</strong> about a decision your husband has made, ask him the following:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>“I’m confused about _________. Can you explain it to me?”</li>
<li>“Can we talk about _____? I feel uncomfortable about ______.”</li>
</ul>
<blockquote dir="ltr"><p>Don’t ask: “WHY in the world would you do it that way?” or ask “Why?” in any way that implies you think he is foolish.</p></blockquote>
<ol type="1">
<li><strong>If you find yourself</strong> thinking negative thoughts about your husband, <em>stop and choose</em> to think of something else – especially things from your positive quality list.</li>
<li><strong>Respect his likes and dislikes.</strong> If he likes a particular food, make a point of serving that regularly. If he hates the color purple, don’t wear purple in his presence. If he likes you to wear perfume, do it.</li>
</ol>
<p>Remember, God is working on you <em>and</em> your husband. You can both learn from your failures as well as your successes. Give God the freedom to teach your husband through failure. In the same way, give God the freedom to teach you to trust Him through your husband’s failure.</p>
<p>Courtesy of <a href="http://christianwomentoday.com/womenmen/respect.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><cite>ChristianWomenToday.com</cite></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Ways You Can Love Your Husband HIS Way</title>
		<link>/100-ways-you-can-love-your-husband-his-way/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 19:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Practical Help]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.allmyrespect.com/?p=28</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Discuss this list with your husband. Ask him to check the ones most meaningful to him and then arrange them in order of importance to him. Use this list as a basis for learning his views. Your relationship can be greatly strengthened as you use these suggestions.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discuss this list with your husband. Ask him to check the ones most meaningful to him and then arrange them in order of importance to him. Use this list as a basis for learning his views. Your relationship can be greatly strengthened as you use these suggestions.<span id="more-28"></span></p>
<p>1. Communicate with him respectfully.<br />
2. Regard him as important and let him know he’s important to you.<br />
3. Purposefully try to understand his feelings—even when you disagree with him.<br />
4. Show interest in his friends giving him some time with them if they’re trust-worthy.<br />
5. Ask for his opinion and let him know you value what he says.<br />
6. Tell him you both love him AND like him.<br />
7. Let him feel your approval and affections.<br />
8. Protect his dignity on a daily basis.<br />
9. Be tender with him realizing he has feelings also.<br />
10. Foster an atmosphere of laughter in your home. Look for ways to laugh together.<br />
11. Avoid sudden major changes without discussion giving him time to adjust.<br />
12. When you go out on a date together don’t bring up problems—have fun instead.<br />
13. Focus on what he’s doing right, instead of focusing so often on the negatives.<br />
14. Show interest in what he feels is important in life.<br />
15. Correct him gently and in private.<br />
16. Recognize that the first few minutes after a spouse comes home often sets the stage for how the rest of the evening will go. So try to make the first few minutes of seeing him a positive experience. (And then ease into the negative if it’s necessary.)<br />
17. Make special time available to him apart from the children.<br />
18. Don’t allow any family member to treat him disrespectfully. Be the one to defend him to any family member that dishonors his place as your husband.<br />
19. Compliment him often.<br />
20. Be creative when you express your love, both in words and in actions.<br />
21. Talk with him about having specific family goals for each year to work on to achieve together so you will both feel closer to each other as a marital team.<br />
22. Don’t over commit yourself. Leave time for him.<br />
23. Extend God’s grace to him and be forgiving when he offends you.<br />
24. Find ways to show him you need him.<br />
25. Give him time to be alone. (This energizes him to reconnect at other times.)<br />
26. Admit your mistakes; don’t be afraid to be humble. Peel away your pride.<br />
27. Defend him to those who disrespectfully talk about him. Remember that love protects (1 Corinthians 13:7).<br />
28. Respect his desire to do well—not his performance.<br />
29. Rub his feet or neck, or scratch his back after a hard day.<br />
30. Take time for the two of you to sit and talk calmly (schedule it when necessary).<br />
31. Initiate going out on romantic outings (when he’s not tired).<br />
32. Email him when he’s at work, telling him how much you love him.<br />
33. Surprise him with a fun gift of some kind that he’d really enjoy.<br />
34. Express how much you appreciate him for working so hard to support the family.<br />
35. Tell him how proud you are of him for who he is (giving him specific reasons).<br />
36. Give advice in a loving way — not in a nagging or belittling way.<br />
37. Help your husband to be the Spiritual head at home (without “lording” it over him).<br />
38. Reserve some energy for him so you’re not so tired when he wants you sexually.<br />
39. Don’t expect him to do projects beyond his natural capabilities.<br />
40. Pray for him to enjoy God’s best in life.<br />
41. Take special notice for what he has done for you and the family.<br />
42. Brag about him to other people both in front of him and even when he’s not there.<br />
43. Share your feelings with him at appropriate times (but keep it brief when he’s tired—sometimes men can feel “flooded” by too many words).<br />
44. Tell him 3 things you specifically appreciate about him.<br />
45. Honor him in front of the children (differ respectfully in private when necessary).<br />
46. Give him time to unwind for a little while after he comes home from work. Arrange ahead of time to take your “time out”, giving him a few minutes with the children.<br />
47. Get up with him, even when he gets up earlier than you want to and pray with him. (Hopefully you can go back to sleep afterwards. If not, it’s a sacrifice worth making.)<br />
48. Be his “help-mate” in whatever ways you sense he needs it.<br />
49. Do some shoulder-to-shoulder activities with him (like watching a movie or taking a drive together) without talking. Sometimes men just like to BE with you and not talk.<br />
50. Be a student of his ways so you show your love in ways he best comprehends it.<br />
51. When your husband is in a bad mood give him time to recover. Don’t crowd him.<br />
52. Help him to finish his goals, hobbies, or education when your see he needs it.<br />
53. Treat him as if God has stamped on his forehead: “Handle With Care.”<br />
54. Work to get rid of habits that annoy him.<br />
55. Be kind and thoughtful to his relatives. Don’t make him choose between you.<br />
56. Don’t compare his relatives with yours in a negative way.<br />
57. Thank him for things he’s done around the house. (It means a lot to men).<br />
58. Don’t expect credit for all you do for him. Do it as “unto the Lord.”<br />
59. Make sure he agrees with everything important that you’re planning to do.<br />
60. Do little things for him—an unexpected kiss, coffee in bed, etc.<br />
61. Don’t belittle his intelligence or be cynical in your words with him.<br />
62. Initiate sex periodically. And respond more often.<br />
63. Sometimes let him enjoy his day off work without having to “work” at home.<br />
64. Get to the point in your discussions. Spare him details unless he wants them.<br />
65. Discover his sexual needs.<br />
66. Surprise him with a 15 second kiss when he gets home from work.<br />
67. Wink at him from across the room when you’re out at a group function.<br />
68. Give him the benefit of the doubt when he mis-speaks.<br />
69. Don’t quarrel over words.<br />
70. Be kind and courteous with him. (Don’t be kinder to strangers than to him.)<br />
71. When things go wrong, instead of assessing blame, focus on how to do better.<br />
72. As a kindness, don’t say, “I told you so.”<br />
73. Try not to argue over money. Peacefully discuss future expenditures instead.<br />
74. Take him out on dates—pre-planning all of the details ahead of time.<br />
75. Hold his hand and snuggle up close to him at times both at home and in public.<br />
76. Praise his good decisions; minimize the bad ones.<br />
77. Tell him you love him more often.<br />
78. Put love notes in his pockets and brief case.<br />
79. Sit with him while he’s watching TV—even if the program doesn’t interest you.<br />
80. Don’t expect him to read your mind. (Family’s are spared grief when a husband isn’t required to read their wife’s mind despite the fact that the wife thinks he should.)<br />
81. Periodically, give him time with his family alone.<br />
82. Check with him before you throw away his papers and stuff. (He may view them as more important than you realize.)<br />
83. Work to keep yourself in shape in every way.<br />
84. Let him express himself freely, without fear of being called stupid or illogical.<br />
85. Carefully choose your words. Remember to “speak the truth in LOVE.”<br />
86. Don’t criticize him in front of others—keeping his dignity in tact.<br />
87. Visit his childhood home with him.<br />
88. When you’re angry, express it in respectful ways. Don’t give the silent treatment.<br />
89. Pray for him.<br />
90. Make him homemade soup when he’s sick.<br />
91. Look your best—dress to honor him and make him proud to be seen with you.<br />
92. Support him when someone tries to put him down. Be his best cheer leader.<br />
93. Don’t disagree with him in front of the children.<br />
94. Take him for a weekend get-away without the children.<br />
95. Cheer his successes whether in business or in other areas of everyday living.<br />
96. Graciously teach him how to demonstrate his love for you.<br />
97. Give him coupons to redeem—maybe for a back scratch or a shoulder rub.<br />
98. Buy him a gift certificate to his favorite lunch spot and put it in his wallet.<br />
99. Hide notes for him around the house where only he will find them.<br />
100. Thank him for just being himself.</p>
<p>Courtesy of <cite><a href="http://www.marriagemissions.com/100-ways-you-can-love-your-husband-his-way/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">MarriageMissions.com</a></cite></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
